[
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/234650/how-old-is-your-wrapping-paper/",
        "answer": "Oh my gosh! Years! I have some paper that my SIL bought me before she was married to my brother and they’ve been married 21 years. It has Boyd Bears on it and I don’t want to use it.\nI also found a bag last year that had a tag on it with my moms name and she’s been gone since 2011.\nSome of my bags are way older than that though.\nFun question!"
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/234516/if-you-are-in-a-christmas-gift-exchange-and-the-rule/",
        "answer": "The spending limit means not above that, not it must be that. Any amount below is acceptable,"
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/234138/if-you-won-a-billion-and-a-half-dollars-what-would/",
        "answer": "Some states allow you to collect the money in secret, but my state isn’t one of those. And I figure someone would figure it out and announce it, so your idea of moving is probably for the best.\nAfter seeking professional advice on tax shelters etc., the sharing comes in.\nFamily would come first and foremost. Friends and coworkers. Then donations to the animal shelters, St. Jude’s childrens hospital and homeless shelters and food banks in my state.\nI would set up a fund to pay all kids breakfast and lunches in my state for as long as the money held out. Even the families that could afford the lunches should get it. That way, the less fortunate wouldn’t be as noticeable. My state is one of the poorest in the nation, so helping get kids food and clothes would take a large portion of my money.\nOf course I would move also, and travel."
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/233377/do-you-buy-gifts-for-friends-and-family-when-you-travel/",
        "answer": "I really haven’t traveled too far from home. But whenever we go to a beach I love to collect seashells and pretty little stones I find and sometimes give them to family. So this may not qualify. I have never been to another country…ooh that would be so cool!"
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/230098/do-you-have-any-interestingsweet-sympathy-gift-ideas/",
        "answer": "You can send a chocolate, or fruit, gift basket. Or ask if she needs anything; Like a maid service, or a delicious casserole dish? Or you can pay for an extra long distance phone call? Or let her stay a week as a guest at a hotel or your house until she gets on her feet?"
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/229897/do-you-honor-birthdays-with-charitable-giving-requests/",
        "answer": "Yeah no."
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/229739/how-long-do-you-keep-birthday-christmas-cards-for/",
        "answer": "i use them as fire starters in my wood stove after Little Christmas"
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/229725/what-is-the-best-or-most-favorite-gift-you-have-ever/",
        "answer": "My mom gave me the best sweaters, very warm and comfortable."
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/227157/what-should-i-buy-for-a-house-warming-gift/",
        "answer": "A furnace?"
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/225737/can-i-use-primer-on-a-cardboard-box-before-using-acrylic/",
        "answer": "As we advised on your earlier and very similar question, just take some other piece of cardboard and try it out."
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/225248/should-i-give-something-else-to-the-neighbors-for-helping-with/",
        "answer": "How did they react to the wine?"
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/224310/how-are-you-expecting-your-christmas-chanukah-and-winter-holidays-will/",
        "answer": "I’ll be staying home on my own. If there are some very mild days, I may have a friend or two over for socializing on the deck."
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/235147/is-my-wine-still-good/",
        "answer": "Safe? Yes. Good? ehhhh… Wine doesn’t like getting hot."
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/234600/so-jellies-lets-discuss-wrapping-do-you-wrap-fancy-or-simple/",
        "answer": "I do wrap. I don’t gift bag. I do it pretty simple. I don’t bother with a bow, but I do sticker-labels. I sometimes use joke wrapping paper or joke gift boxes even though they’re more expensive just to add an extra thing to talk about and have happen on the day."
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/234339/do-you-shop-during-the-thanksgiving-weekend-sales/",
        "answer": "Oh, lordy, never ever ever. I used to work retail, and I still hate the general frenetic miasma of the holiday sales weekends. I am a bit in awe of anyone willing to brave the crowds. It doesn’t help that I am barely 5’ tall, and bustling crowds make me feel like a lost toddler."
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/233441/what-would-you-do-in-this-birthday-party-situation/",
        "answer": "I have found similar experiences to what you described, @janbb. Most people bring gifts and then I feel like an idiot. My suggestion, and what I will be doing in the future, is a gift card for a book store and maybe a small fun book in a gift bag. If, in the unlikely event that nobody else has brought a gift, you can kind of slip the gift to the host by placing it in a corner, quietly."
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/231053/have-you-ever-heard-of-parents-giving-their-children-presents-for/",
        "answer": "Yes, but not at the level of Christmas or their Birthday. We always have my daughter Spring/Summer stuff, like a tee-shirt and flip flops or a beach towel and swim goggles. It had to fit in her basket though, along with some candy and such."
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/229992/what-sort-of-company-makes-wrapping-paper-with-titanic-printed-on/",
        "answer": "Like this = = = > https://www.zazzle.com/titanic+ship+wrapping+paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/229745/did-you-buy-a-gift-for-yourself-this-year/",
        "answer": "A nice set of kitchen knives. I haven’t had the pleasure in years. Each time I got a new set my daughter would lose them, use them as lockpicks and screwdrivers, or, maybe I don’t want to know what happened to the others.\nThe set I bought are nothing expensive, but nice."
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/229738/what-do-you-call-giving-a-card-to-someone/",
        "answer": "I call giving a card to someone, giving a card to someone."
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/229521/is-it-really-important-to-you-to-exchange-holiday-gifts-with/",
        "answer": "No. It was especially difficult when I had no money.\nI have no problem not receiving gifts, either.\nAnd your coworker is obtuse."
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/226097/after-a-divorce-or-a-major-breakup-what-have-you-done/",
        "answer": "I have kept all the stuff that I/we shared when we were still together and I relish them as reminders, remembrances of how it was.\nSome I still take with me on travels, as good luck charms (also keepsakes from other people, other than my then partner).\nI should add that my ex partner and myself are friends, still."
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/225702/can-you-use-watercolor-pencils-on-cardboard/",
        "answer": "Sure you can. Whether the colors will actually be vivid enough to show, I don’t know. Try it on another piece of cardboard if you don’t want to try it on the box."
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/224624/what-kind-of-gifts-if-any-do-you-exchange-with-your/",
        "answer": "Last year we had a white elephant exchange, people brought wrapped presents, and we got numbers telling us who chose first. Some of the gifts were very nice, some silly, some goofy. It was a lot of fun."
    },
    {
        "question": "https://www.fluther.com/224218/tis-the-season-does-your-holiday-gift-list-have-fewer-people/",
        "answer": "Not really. The only time I buy Christmas gifts is if I’m doing Christmas with my husband’s family or small gifts if I’m invited to a gift exchange. We aren’t going anywhere for Christmas this year."
    }
]